A Guide to the William Garber Photograph Collection, 1930-1960
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0259; 2x2.5
  Housed with 0260-1
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0260; 2x2.5
  Housed with 0259 and 0261.
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0261; 2x2.5
  Housed with 0259-60.
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0262; 2x2.5
  Housed with 0263-4.
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0263; 2x2.5
  Housed with 0262, 0264.
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0264; 2x2.5
  Housed with 0262-3.
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0265; 2x2.5
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0266; 2x2.5
- Bends of the Shenandoah River and the surrounding area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0267; 2x2.5
- Rockingham Poultry building.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0268; 2.25x3.25
  Series 11c, “Aerial Photographs: Rockingham Poultry,” begins.
- Rockingham Poultry buildings, and surrounding area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0269; 5x7
- Rockingham Poultry buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0270; 5x7
- Distant view of the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds in Woodstock, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0271; 4x5
  Series 11d, “Aerial Photographs: Shenandoah County Fair,” begins. Also see Series 7e and 8d.
- The horse track at the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0272; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0273; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002. 04.0274; 4x5
  Film seems to be faded or double exposed.
- Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va. Close up of the carnival side. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0275; 4x5
- Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va. Close up of the carnival side. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0276; 4x5
- Horse track and parking at the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0277; 4x5
- Distant view of the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0278; 4x5
  Film seems to be faded or double exposed. Some blue spotting due to film deterioration.
- Distant view of the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0279; 4x5
  Film seems to be faded, or may have had exposure to water.
- Distant view of the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0280; 4x5
- Distant view of the Shenandoah County Fairgrounds. Woodstock, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0281; 4x5
- View of Maury Hall, Varner House, Jackson Hall, Harrison Hall, Logan Hall, and Converse Hall and Bluestone Drive of James Madison University. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1951., Image: P0002.04.0282; 4x5
  Series 11e, “Aerial Photographs: JMU and Other College Campuses,” begins.
- Distant view of the Bluestone campus of James Madison University. Harrisonburg, Va. After 1953., Image: P0002.04.0283; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0283.After 1953., Image: P0002.04.0283a; 4x5
- View of Maury Hall, Varner House, Jackson Hall, Harrison Hall, Logan Hall, and Converse Hall and Bluestone Drive of James Madison University, with parts of the plane blocking the view. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1951., Image: P0002.04.0284; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0284.After 1951., Image: P0002.04.0284a; 4x5
- Memorial Hall of JMU, or Old Harrisonburg High School. Harrisonburg, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0285; 4x5
- Alternate view of Memorial Hall of JMU, or Old Harrisonburg High School. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0286; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0287; 4x5
  “EMC” handwritten on the side of the negative. Eastern Mennonite College?
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0288; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0289; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0290; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus, with the plane obstructing the view. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0291; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0291.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0291a; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0291.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0291b.; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0291.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0291.; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0292; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0293; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0294; 4x5
- A number of large buildings, probably of the Eastern Mennonite University campus. Harrisonburg, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0295; 4x5
- A number of houses and public buildings in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0296; 4x5
  Series 11f, “Aerial Photographs: Luray, Va,” begins.
- Residential and public areas of Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0297; 4x5
- A house in the middle of a large wooded area. Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0298; 4x5
- Houses and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0299; 4x5
- Houses and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0300; 4x5
- Houses and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0301; 4x5
- Houses and farmland in Luray, Va.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0302; 4x5
- Houses and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0303; 4x5
- Farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0304; 4x5
- Farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0305; 4x5
- Farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0306; 4x5
- Farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0307; 4x5
- Farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0308; 4x5
- Houses in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0309; 4x5
- Houses in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0310; 4x5
- Houses and farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0311; 4x5
- Public and residential areas near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0312; 4x5
- Houses and farmland near Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0313; 4x5
- Urban areas and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0314; 4x5
- Urban areas and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0315; 4x5
- Urban areas and farmland in Luray, Va. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0316; 4x5
- Overhead view of a field full of trees; maybe a tree farm.1950, Image: P0002.04.0317; 2.5x2.5
  Series 11g, “Aerial Photographs: Images Taken from Jack Reynold’s Plane (see Series 10b),” begins.
- Overhead view of a possible tree farm.1950, Image: P0002.04.0318; 2.5x2.5
- Overhead view of a possible tree farm.1950, Image: P0002.04.0319; 2.5x2.5
- A number of farm or industrial buildings.1950, Image: P0002.04.0320; 2.5x2.5
- A number of farm or industrial buildings.1950, Image: P0002.04.0321; 2.5x2.5
- A number of houses surrounded by fields and gardens.1950, Image: P0002.04.0322; 2.5x2.5
- Distant view of two water towers.1950, Image: P0002.04.0323; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0324.
- Distant view of two water towers.1950, Image: P0002.04.0324; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0323.
- Public or industrial buildings.1950, Image: P0002.04.0325; 2.5x2.5
- Public or industrial buildings.1950, Image: P0002.04.0326; 2.5x2.5
- Farm or industrial buildings, with two water towers in the distance.1950, Image: P0002.04.0327; 2.5x2.5
- Farm or industrial buildings, with two water towers in the distance. 1950, Image: P0002.04.0328; 2.5x2.5
- Fields and farmland.1950, Image: P0002.04.0329; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0330.
- Fields and farmland.1950, Image: P0002.04.0330; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0329.
- Fields, farmland, and a water tower.1950, Image: P0002.04.0331; 2.5x2.5
- Fields, farmland, and a water tower.1950, Image: P0002.04.0332; 2.5x2.5
- A number of public or industrial buildings.1950, Image: P0002.04.0333; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0334.
- A number of public or industrial buildings. 1950, Image: P0002.04.0334; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0333.
- View of a possible tree farm near a public road/highway.1950, Image: P0002.04.0335; 2.5x2.5
- Distant view of private and public buildings surrounded by farmland.1950, Image: P0002.04.0336; 4x5
- Gardens and farmland.1950, Image: P0002.04.0337; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0338.
- A number of public or industrial buildings.1950, Image: P0002.04.0338; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0337.
- Fields and farmland.1950, Image: P0002.04.0339; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0340. Film is very faded.
- View of a tree; perhaps testing the film or camera.1950, Image: P0002.04.0340; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0339. Film is very dark.
- A number of public or industrial buildings next to two water towers. 1950, Image: P0002.04.0341; 2.5x2.5
- A possible tree farm.1950, Image: P0002.04.0342; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0343.
- Public or industrial buildings, surrounded by farmland. 1950, Image: P0002.04.0343.; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0342.
- Close up of large trucks loading or unloading a large pile of gravel or dirt.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344; 2.5x2.5
  Series 11h, “Aerial Photographs: Miscellaneous,” begins.
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344a; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344b; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344c; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344d; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344e; 2.5x2.5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344f; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0344g.
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0344.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0344g; 2.5x2.5
  Housed with 0344f.
- Expansive view of fields and farmland, with mountains in the distance. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0345; 4x5
- A number of public or industrial buildings next to two water towers.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0346; 2.5x2.5
- View of a residential area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0347; 4x5
- A number of private and public buildings, with mountains in the distance.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0348; 4x5
- Expansive view of houses, fields, and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0349; 4x5
- Houses, fields, and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0350; 4x5
- Houses, fields, and farmland, with mountains in the distance.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0351; 4x5
- Busy public buildings with fields and farmland in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0352; 4x5
- A number of public buildings with fields and a wooded area in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0353; 4x5
- A number of farm or industrial buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0354; 4x5
- A number of private and public buildings with fields and a wooded area in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0355; 4x5
- A number of public and private buildings, surrounded by fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0356; 4x5
- Farming or industrial buildings, with an expansive view of fields and mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0357; 4x5
- An expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains, with industrial or farming buildings in the foreground. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0358; 4x5
- An expansive view of fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0359; 4x5
- Large public buildings surrounded by houses and farms.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0360; 4x5
- An expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0361; 4x5
- Farm houses and fields, with mountains in the background, possibly near New Market.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0362; 4x5
- Farms, fields, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0363; 4x5
- An expansive view of farms and fields.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0364; 4x5
  Film seems to have faded.
- A number of large farms, with mountains in the distance.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0365; 4x5
- A large farm, with a number of other farms in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0366; 4x5
- Expansive view of farmland, fields, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0367; 4x5
- Expansive view of farmland, fields, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0368; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0369; 4x5
- Private and public buildings surrounded by large fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0370; 4x5
- Close up view of a large farm.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0371; 4x5
- Private and public buildings with a large field and wooded area in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0372; 4x5
- Close up view of a number of public and private buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0373; 4x5
- View of a large residential area with farmland and mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0374; 4x5
- View of a large residential area with farmland and mountains in the background. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0375; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0376; 4x5
  Film seems to be faded.
- Expansive view of fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0377; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0378; 4x5
- Fields, farmland, and mountains, with view partially obstructed by the airplane.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0379; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0380; 4x5
- A number of houses surrounded by fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0381; 4x5
- Close up view of a large church, graveyard, and farm, with other houses and farms in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0382; 4x5
- An expansive view of farmland with mountains in the distance.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0383; 4x5
- View of both public and private buildings, and a water tower.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0384; 4x5
- Farm or industrial buildings, with mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0385; 4x5
- Farm or industrial buildings, with mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0386; 4x5
- A farmhouse surrounded by crops and fields.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0387; 4x5
- Fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0388; 4x5
- Fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0389; 4x5
- View of various farms that is obstructed by a part of the plane.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0390; 4x5
- Fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0391; 4x5
  Film is very dark.
- Close up view of a farm that is partially obstructed by a part of the plane.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0392; 2.5x3.5
- A number of public and private structures with an expansive view of farmland and mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0393; 2.5x3.5
- View of a large farm surrounded by fields, crops, and with mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0394; 2.5x3.5
- Farm or industrial buildings surrounded by fields and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0395; 4x5
- Close up view of a large farm.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0396; 4x5
- One house in the middle of a large wooded area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0397; 4x5
- A farm next to a wooded area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0398; 4x5
- Duplicate of P0002.04.0398.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0398a; 4x5
- A number of houses next to a large farm.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0399; 4x5
- View of private and public buildings near a water tower.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0400; 4x5
- Close up view of Broadway Motor Company, Inc.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0401; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0402; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0403; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0404; 4x5
- Expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0405; 4x5
  There is a small scratch in the center of the negative.
- Expansive view of fields, farmland, and mountains.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0406; 4x5
- A number of industrial or farm buildings surrounded by crops and fields.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0407; 4x5
- A number of industrial or farm buildings surrounded by crops and fields.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0408; 4x5
- A number of public buildings surrounded by farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0409; 4x5
- Large public or industrial buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0410; 4x5
- Industrial buildings, farmland, and wooded areas.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0411; 4x5
- Close up view of a small house.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0412; 4x5
- A number of houses near the highway.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0413; 4x5
- Two houses divided by a highway.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0414; 4x5
- A small building surrounded by fields and on the side of a main highway.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0415; 4x5
- Close up view of a house and its surrounding farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0416; 4x5
- Close up view of a small collection of houses, possibly a small roadside motel.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0417; 4x5
- Close up view of a large farm.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0418; 4x5
- Close up view of a large farmhouse and its associated buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0419; 4x5
- Collection of small buildings on the side of the road, possibly a small roadside motel. After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0420; 4x5
- An expansive view of a major highway surrounded by fields and farmland, with mountains in the distance.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0421; 4x5
- Close up view of a large farmhouse with its associated buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0422; 4x5
- Close up view of a service station on the side of the road.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0423; 4x5
- A collection of small houses and large stables or barns.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0424; 4x5
- A number of large houses near a major road.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0425; 4x5
- A number of houses separated by a road.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0426; 4x5
- A variety of small houses, with an automotive shop to the far right.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0427; 4x5
- An expansive view of both public and private buildings, with farmland and mountains in the background.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0428; 4x5
- Close up view of a variety of public and private buildings, separated by a major road.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0429; 4x5
- Expansive view of both public and private buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0430; 4x5
- An expansive view of a residential neighborhood.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0431; 4x5
- A large public buildings, possibly a restaurant or store, surrounded by houses, fields, and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0432; 4x5
- A large industrial or farming building, surrounded by houses, fields, and farmland.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0433; 4x5
- A very large industrial or public building near a major road.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0434; 4x5
- Close up view of a collection of farm buildings.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0435; 4x5
- A number of industrial or public buildings near a water tower.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0436; 4x5
- A number of industrial or public buildings near a major road.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0437; 4x5
- An expansive view of a variety of both public and private structures.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0438; 5x7
- An expansive view of a major highway intersecting a residential area.After 1946., Image: P0002.04.0439; 5x7
- A copy of The National Geographic Magazine, Vol. XCVI, no. 1, July 1949. Contains an article about the Shenandoah Valley; may contain Garber’s work, but he is not cited.1949, Image: P0002.05.0001; 7x9.5
  Series 12, “Ephemera: Box 5, Folder 2,” begins.
- View of a street with Pete’s Restaurant and Dove’s Candy shop on the side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0002; 8x10
  Series 13a: “Photograph Prints: Streetscapes and Storefronts, Box 5, Folder 3,” begins.
- View from the middle of a street, with a movie theater and a number of other stores on either side. Probably Broadway, Va. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0003; 8x10
- View from the middle of the street, with Pete’s Restaurant on the left and a number of other buildings on either side.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0004; 8x10
- Three restaurants or other public buildings, viewed from the street.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0005; 8x10
- Front view of a Gulf service station. New Market, Va.c. 1940-1949, Image: P0002.05.0006; 8x10
  “New Market” handwritten in pencil on the back of the photograph.
- Front view of Stroop’s Snake Farm. Probably Edinburg, Va.c. 1945-1955, Image: P0002.05.0007; 8x10
- Inside of a business, probably a general or drug store. View of a counter with bar stools and a large Coca-Cola advertisement.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0008; 8x10
- A woman and two children shopping inside of a grocery store. She has Dr. Pepper in her cart, is standing next to a display for Dr. Pepper, and there is a Dr. Pepper delivery man in the background.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0009; 8x10
  Series 13b, “Photograph Prints: The Grocery Store and Dr. Pepper, Box 5, Folder 4” begins.
- A woman, three young children, and a Dr. Pepper delivery man standing next to a wall of shelves filled with cereals inside of a grocery store.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0010; 8x10
- Inside of an automotive store; view of the main counter and cash register, with an advertisement for Ford auto parts.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0011; 8x10
  Series 13c, “Photograph Prints: Automotive Shops, Box 5, Folder 5,” begins.
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0011.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0011a; 8x10
- Inside of an automotive store; view of the main counter and cash register, with a small office to the side. Advertisement for Ford auto parts above the counter. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0012; 8x10
- Duplicate of P0002.05.0012.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0012a; 8x10
- Moyers Motor Company, view from the street with a “Grand Opening” banner hanging in the front. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0013; 8x10
- Four men posing outside of Moyer’s Motor Company, next to an Esso motor oil display.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0014; 8x10
- Top of an Esso motor oil display.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0015; 8x10
- Inside view of an automotive shop.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0016; 8x10
- Two women and a man standing in the doorway of a crowded building, holding keys that say “The Key to Good Car” on the side. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0017; 8x10
- Two men, one standing and one crouching, outside of an automotive shop next to an advertisement for Gulf tires.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0018; 8x10
- Two men standing in a large chicken coup with a large number of chickens. c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0019; 8x10
  Series 13d, “Photograph Prints: Poultry, Box 5, Folder 6,” begins.
- Six men in suits standing inside of a large barn with a large number of baby chickens. Gene Runion’s farm, Mt. Jackson, Va.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0020; 8x10
  “Farm of Gene Runion, Mt. Jackson, Va.” handwritten in pen on the back.
- Five men and one small child posing with a Heinz Nu-Way Feeds truck.c. 1930-1950, Image: P0002.05.0021; 8x10
  Series 13e, “Photograph Prints: Triplett and Vehrencamp Trucks, Box 5, Folder 7,” begins.